<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on Portfolio website of Martino Armanini</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on Portfolio website of Martino Armanini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliquam</title>
      <link>/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magna</title>
      <link>/blogs/magna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Manufacturers in the NYSE</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Returns of financial automotive stocks In this little reasearch, Lorenzo, an Italian patriot, has asked us to analyse the financial performances of the automotive companies in the NYSE. He firmly beleieves that “the italians are better” and, thus will be more attractive to the stock market. Thanks to this curiosity we will dive into the financial markets, we will search for the Automotive companies’ stocks and compare them with a Risk and Return graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to know your delays</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog7/</guid>
      <description>Getting up in the air Flying is one of the comforts that we have all lost in the first months of 2020. It is for this reason that I have started looking into the cracks of the industry as soon as I had the chance and ability to manipulate data with R. I might have felt that doing this analysis would bring me closer to the feeling of freedom that I would have when taking a flight to another continent of country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What pay discrimination looks like, for real</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog3/</guid>
      <description>Pay discrimination as a social issue In the recent years, pay discrimination and specifically gender discrimination has been raised a very relevant social issue.
Today, we’ll try to look into it in more detail though the lens of Omega Group Plc. A quick analysis of a sample of 50 employees (of which 24 men and 26 women) revealed that the average salary for men was about 8,700 higher than for women.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>